[{"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/4.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/10.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/10.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/4.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/5.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/5.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/6.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/4.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/6.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/3.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/4.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/3.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/3.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/6.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/4.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/3.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/4.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/10.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/10.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/4.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/4.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/10.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/6.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/6.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/4.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/4.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/10.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/5.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/5.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/10.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/5.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/5.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/5.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/5.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/3.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/3.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/3.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/3.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/3.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/5.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/5.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/3.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/4.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/4.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/5.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/5.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/6.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/6.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/6.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填", "houseImgType": "2", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/3.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/3.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/11.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/9.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/6.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "houseImgType": "1", "personImg": [["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/6.svg"], ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/7.svg"]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/6.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": ["v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/1.svg"]}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input6", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-04"}]